[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 31, "question": "And Dick Morris, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Dick", "Morris", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "I'm a little battered and bleeding, but --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "little", "battered", "and", "bleeding", ",", "but", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Morris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Is there any rational explanation for why you got it so wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "rational", "explanation", "for", "why", "you", "got", "it", "so", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I absolutely believed it, and so did a lot of people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "believed", "it", ",", "and", "so", "did", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "How can a pundit who is as experienced as you, with great respect, be so wrong when this guy just sits on his computer, crunching the numbers and data, and gets it completely right?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "a", "pundit", "who", "is", "as", "experienced", "as", "you", ",", "with", "great", "respect", ",", "be", "so", "wrong", "when", "this", "guy", "just", "sits", "on", "his", "computer", ",", "crunching", "the", "numbers", "and", "data", ",", "and", "gets", "it", "completely", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, (INAUDIBLE) when he was a mayor of New York, said, I don't make many mistakes, but when I make them, it's a beaut.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "when", "he", "was", "a", "mayor", "of", "New", "York", ",", "said", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "make", "many", "mistakes", ",", "but", "when", "I", "make", "them", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "beaut", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "How does that make you feel, given you've been so respected for so long until this period?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", ",", "given", "you", "'ve", "been", "so", "respected", "for", "so", "long", "until", "this", "period", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, I have gotten 30 senators and governors elected, 14 presidents and prime ministers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "gotten", "30", "senators", "and", "governors", "elected", ",", "14", "presidents", "and", "prime", "ministers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "You mean Hurricane Sandy?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "Hurricane", "Sandy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Well, I prefer to believe that CNN's polling was accurate, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "prefer", "to", "believe", "that", "CNN", "'s", "polling", "was", "accurate", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I think all the polls should be taken with a large pinch of salt.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "all", "the", "polls", "should", "be", "taken", "with", "a", "large", "pinch", "of", "salt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Was that why FOX let you go?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "why", "FOX", "let", "you", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "No, but --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger Ales"]}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "But they must have told you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "they", "must", "have", "told", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Well, I had a wonderful talk with Roger Ales, who I really respect, a week ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "a", "wonderful", "talk", "with", "Roger", "Ales", ",", "who", "I", "really", "respect", ",", "a", "week", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Why have you been singled out?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "been", "singled", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "But do you know the answer?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "know", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Do you resent the decision?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "resent", "the", "decision", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Look, FOX has given me the opportunity of a lifetime.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "FOX", "has", "given", "me", "the", "opportunity", "of", "a", "lifetime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", ":"], "qSentId": 215, "question": "It's got to annoy you that Karl Rove gets to stay there, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "got", "to", "annoy", "you", "that", "Karl", "Rove", "gets", "to", "stay", "there", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Piers, when --", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "when", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karl Rove"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Should the party's stand then for a woman's right to choose was to trying to keep the numbers low, is that what you're saying?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "the", "party", "'s", "stand", "then", "for", "a", "woman", "'s", "right", "to", "choose", "was", "to", "trying", "to", "keep", "the", "numbers", "low", ",", "is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "No, I'm saying that they're not going to do that, and that's their opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "saying", "that", "they", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "do", "that", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "their", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Where does the party stand?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "the", "party", "stand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "But what I am --", "answer_tokens": ["But", "what", "I", "am", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What's the Republican position then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "Republican", "position", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Pro life.", "answer_tokens": ["Pro", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What you're saying is, they need to move from pro life to pro choice, albeit trying to reduce the numbers?", "question_tokens": ["What", "you", "'re", "saying", "is", ",", "they", "need", "to", "move", "from", "pro", "life", "to", "pro", "choice", ",", "albeit", "trying", "to", "reduce", "the", "numbers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "No, you're not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "-- that so many states are moving that way?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "so", "many", "states", "are", "moving", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "My view on gay marriage is that if a state decides to go for gay marriage, the legislature of the voters, that's great.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "view", "on", "gay", "marriage", "is", "that", "if", "a", "state", "decides", "to", "go", "for", "gay", "marriage", ",", "the", "legislature", "of", "the", "voters", ",", "that", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What's your personal view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "personal", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I don't believe that the court should jam it down anybody's throat.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "that", "the", "court", "should", "jam", "it", "down", "anybody", "'s", "throat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What's your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "That if people want it, they should be able to do it, but it's got to be a decision of the community.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "if", "people", "want", "it", ",", "they", "should", "be", "able", "to", "do", "it", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "got", "to", "be", "a", "decision", "of", "the", "community", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "It can't have endless people on both sides ripping each other's position apart, so that people (INAUDIBLE) when it comes to an election, people go, what do they actually stand for?", "question_tokens": ["It", "ca", "n't", "have", "endless", "people", "on", "both", "sides", "ripping", "each", "other", "'s", "position", "apart", ",", "so", "that", "people", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "an", "election", ",", "people", "go", ",", "what", "do", "they", "actually", "stand", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "What we do stand for, Republicans do stand for, and it's becoming very clear, and we need to be much stronger on this, is holding down spending and debt.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "we", "do", "stand", "for", ",", "Republicans", "do", "stand", "for", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "becoming", "very", "clear", ",", "and", "we", "need", "to", "be", "much", "stronger", "on", "this", ",", "is", "holding", "down", "spending", "and", "debt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Should Boehner - should he be replaced?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "Boehner", "-", "should", "he", "be", "replaced", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, I don't -- a fight of that sort now would be destructive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "a", "fight", "of", "that", "sort", "now", "would", "be", "destructive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Where do you start with all that?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "start", "with", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, I thought he was graceful, first of all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "he", "was", "graceful", ",", "first", "of", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Never mind specific weapons, but the culture of gun violence that has enveloped America?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "mind", "specific", "weapons", ",", "but", "the", "culture", "of", "gun", "violence", "that", "has", "enveloped", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, I -- you know, I think we have to really start with the laws.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "we", "have", "to", "really", "start", "with", "the", "laws", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "But is there a will amongst the politicians, Kerry Kennedy, to get this done?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "there", "a", "will", "amongst", "the", "politicians", ",", "Kerry", "Kennedy", ",", "to", "get", "this", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I was up on Capitol Hill today, and speaking to 15 members of Congress, and all of whom have said that they are for this legislation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "up", "on", "Capitol", "Hill", "today", ",", "and", "speaking", "to", "15", "members", "of", "Congress", ",", "and", "all", "of", "whom", "have", "said", "that", "they", "are", "for", "this", "legislation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kerry Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "What is your solution or idea for how to reduce gun violence in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "solution", "or", "idea", "for", "how", "to", "reduce", "gun", "violence", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, the most important thing is to keep lethal weapons out of the hands of criminals and the mentally ill and people who would perpetrate that violence.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "is", "to", "keep", "lethal", "weapons", "out", "of", "the", "hands", "of", "criminals", "and", "the", "mentally", "ill", "and", "people", "who", "would", "perpetrate", "that", "violence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What is the big deal in extending the limitation, in the light of these mass shootings, to include assault weapons, assault rifles?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "big", "deal", "in", "extending", "the", "limitation", ",", "in", "the", "light", "of", "these", "mass", "shootings", ",", "to", "include", "assault", "weapons", ",", "assault", "rifles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, the AR-15 is a civilian version of the military rifle, and is widely owned legally by the civilian community right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "AR-15", "is", "a", "civilian", "version", "of", "the", "military", "rifle", ",", "and", "is", "widely", "owned", "legally", "by", "the", "civilian", "community", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What is the argument against banning them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "argument", "against", "banning", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "They're not the military version.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "not", "the", "military", "version", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "How does it feel to be an icon?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "feel", "to", "be", "an", "icon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "I'm not sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kanye West"]}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Of all your amazing successes with all these incredible artists, what's the one, if could I relive it for you again -- you have like five minutes to live and I could say you can have one moment with any of these artists, which one would you go for?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "your", "amazing", "successes", "with", "all", "these", "incredible", "artists", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "one", ",", "if", "could", "I", "relive", "it", "for", "you", "again", "--", "you", "have", "like", "five", "minutes", "to", "live", "and", "I", "could", "say", "you", "can", "have", "one", "moment", "with", "any", "of", "these", "artists", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "go", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ",", "IN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Incredible moment, Kanye West in my office rapping his entire album to me, just like we're sitting here, right.", "answer_tokens": ["Incredible", "moment", ",", "Kanye", "West", "in", "my", "office", "rapping", "his", "entire", "album", "to", "me", ",", "just", "like", "we", "'re", "sitting", "here", ",", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "ORGAN: Did you know the moment you heard it, this would be huge?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "know", "the", "moment", "you", "heard", "it", ",", "this", "would", "be", "huge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Is the Kim Kardashian move good for his brand or devastating?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "Kim", "Kardashian", "move", "good", "for", "his", "brand", "or", "devastating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I think it is great for his brand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "great", "for", "his", "brand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kim Kardashian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"]}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Let's talk about Beyonce quickly, the lip syncing debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "talk", "about", "Beyonce", "quickly", ",", "the", "lip", "syncing", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "It had to be, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "had", "to", "be", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "I would think.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Who is the worst judge on television at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "worst", "judge", "on", "television", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Oh, dear.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "dear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "You know, I did it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "did", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Who is your money on for big award winners?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "your", "money", "on", "for", "big", "award", "winners", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Without really being specific to categories, I can tell you the songs that really sort of resonated with me.", "answer_tokens": ["Without", "really", "being", "specific", "to", "categories", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "the", "songs", "that", "really", "sort", "of", "resonated", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]